{
  "results": [
    {
      "question": "1. resource calendar",
      "correct_answer": "b. specifies default working and nonworking times for a resource, a project, or a task",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. the maximum capacity of a resource to accomplish tasks",
        "c. when and how much of a resource's time can be assigned to work on tasks",
        "d. the people and equipment that do work to accomplish the tasks of the project"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "2. Max. Units",
      "correct_answer": "h. a resource that doesn't depend on the amount of work on a task or the duration of a task",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "b. specifies default working and nonworking times for a resource, a project, or a task",
        "d. the people and equipment that do work to accomplish the tasks of the project",
        "e. the people, equipment, money, and materials used to complete the tasks in a project"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3. material resource",
      "correct_answer": "g. consumable items used up as the tasks in a project are accomplished",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. the maximum capacity of a resource to accomplish tasks",
        "b. specifies default working and nonworking times for a resource, a project, or a task",
        "i. the base calendar that provides default working times for an entire project"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "4. project calendar",
      "correct_answer": "i. the base calendar that provides default working times for an entire project",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "b. specifies default working and nonworking times for a resource, a project, or a task",
        "j. defines the working and nonworking time for an individual resource",
        "f. a way of documenting information about resources, tasks, and assignments"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "5. cost resource",
      "correct_answer": "e. the people, equipment, money, and materials used to complete the tasks in a project",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "b. specifies default working and nonworking times for a resource, a project, or a task",
        "c. when and how much of a resource's time can be assigned to work on tasks",
        "d. the people and equipment that do work to accomplish the tasks of the project"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "6. work resource",
      "correct_answer": "a. way of documenting information about resources, tasks, and assignments",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. the maximum capacity of a resource to accomplish tasks",
        "b. specifies default working and nonworking times for a resource, a project, or a task",
        "e. the people, equipment, money, and materials used to complete the tasks in a project"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "7. base calendar",
      "correct_answer": "j. defines the working and nonworking time for an individual resource",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "b. specifies default working and nonworking times for a resource, a project, or a task",
        "c. when and how much of a resource's time can be assigned to work on tasks",
        "h. a resource that doesn't depend on the amount of work on a task or the duration of a task"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "8. availability",
      "correct_answer": "c. when and how much of a resource's time can be assigned to work on tasks",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "b. specifies default working and nonworking times for a resource, a project, or a task",
        "d. the people and equipment that do work to accomplish the tasks of the project",
        "e. the people, equipment, money, and materials used to complete the tasks in a project"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "9. resources",
      "correct_answer": "d. the people and equipment that do work to accomplish the tasks of the project",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. the maximum capacity of a resource to accomplish tasks",
        "b. specifies default working and nonworking times for a resource, a project, or a task",
        "f. a way of documenting information about resources, tasks, and assignments"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "10. note",
      "correct_answer": "f. a way of documenting information about resources, tasks, and assignments",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. the maximum capacity of a resource to accomplish tasks",
        "b. specifies default working and nonworking times for a resource, a project, or a task",
        "e. the people, equipment, money, and materials used to complete the tasks in a project"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not an example of a work resource?",
      "correct_answer": "keyboard",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Yan Li",
        "SD card",
        "electrician"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "It is helpful to assign a base calendar to a group of resources when they all __________.",
      "correct_answer": "work the night shift",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "have the same pay rate",
        "have the same Max. Units",
        "do the same job function?"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "A resource calendar does not apply to which of the following?",
      "correct_answer": "material resources",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "people resources",
        "equipment resources",
        "work resources"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "In which of the following views can you view information for the individual people who will perform the tasks on the project?",
      "correct_answer": "Resource Sheet view",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Calendar view",
        "Gantt Chart view",
        "Network Diagram view"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "You can provide additional information about how a resource is scheduled by doing which of the following?",
      "correct_answer": "adding a resource note",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "changing the Max. Units",
        "establishing a project calendar",
        "setting constraints"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "For which resource is the standard rate listed per tracking unit of consumption?",
      "correct_answer": "all of the above",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "material",
        "equipment",
        "people"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "If you have four electricians whom can each work part\u2010time (4 hours rather than 8), which of the following values should you assign to Max. Units for the resource \u201celectrician\u201d?",
      "correct_answer": "50%",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "25%",
        "100%",
        "200%"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "If you assign a base calendar to a resource, which of the following is true?",
      "correct_answer": "The base calendar gives the basic days/hours for the resource, but the resource's calendar can have exceptions to those days/hours.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The base calendar dictates the resource's vacation days.",
        "The base calendar gives all the available time to work on the project.",
        "The resource calendar contains all nonworking days for the entire project."
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "To add vacation days to the calendar for an individual work resource, which dialog box would you use?",
      "correct_answer": "Change Working Time",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Resource Information",
        "Resource Notes",
        "none of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a reason why it is often difficult to get cost information for people resources?",
      "correct_answer": "The information is often confidential.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The information is too complex to calculate.",
        "The information changes too frequently.",
        "The costs are large in comparison with other resource costs."
      ]
    }
  ],
  "setCount": 1
}